#### **ABOUT**

Enthusiastic, highly motivated, organised, communicative, focused on aim. Has been passioned about technology since being a teenager. Has lived in the United Kingdom since 2020 and has worked in the logistics industry for over two years.

#### CONTACT



natalia.sokolowska12@gmail.com



07395 830106



nataliasokolowska.co.uk



Long Eaton, Nottingham

#### REFERENCES



Ela Lisowska
General Manager
Pitman Training Centre
Stuart House
St John's Street
PE1 5DD
01733 315 814
peterborough@pitmantraning.com



HR Department
Amazon Service UK
East Midlands Gateway
Kegworth
Derbyshire
DE74 2DL
sharedservies@amazon.co.uk

# NATALIA SOKOLOWSKA

WEB DEVELOPER

#### **OBJECTIVE**

Quality-focused and result-driven professional seeking a position as a web developer.

#### **WORK HISTORY**

#### PROCESS GUIDE/PROBLEM SOLVER

Amazon EMA1

(11/2021 - 02/2023)

- Investigate and resolve production issues
- Replacing damaged products in customer orders
- Maintain a good workflow in the department according to team leaders' and managers' advice and standards
- Reporting and resolving employee issues or conflicts following company protocols
- Special recognition pin winner "Fulfil Your Potential" productivity and carrying out the critical role in the department

#### **FULFILMENT ASSOCIATE**

Amazon EMA1

(07/2021 - 10/2021)

- Pick and pack customer orders, ensuring a high level of quality and productivity
- Accurately packing and shipping customer orders
- Abiding by health, safety and production standards

#### WAREHOUSE OPERATIVE/ADMIN

**XPO** Logistics

(06/2020 - 05/2021)

- Pick and pack customer orders according to highquality standards
- Checking for wrong or damaged products in customer orders
- Investigate and resolve billing and service discrepancies
- Abiding by health, safety and production standards

#### **SKILLS**

- Driving License cat. B
- Microsoft Office
- Visual Studio
- Visual Studio Code
- GIMP
- Adobe Photoshop
- Adobe Illustrator
- GitHub
- Polish Language
- English Language
- Strong organisational skills
- Excellent workload and time management skills
- Team-working
- Microsoft Azure

#### MANAGER/CUSTOMER ADVISER

Kakadu Studio Koloru, Poland (07/2018 - 03/2020)

- Advice and help customers with choosing products with high-quality standards
- Prepare customer orders according to guidelines
- Inventorying and controlling stocks
- Manage a team of two customers advisors and cooperation with accounting
- Abiding by health, safety and production standards
- My biggest accomplishments were improving the company's social media presence and delivering a finished website that directly contributed to improvement in the company's financial results at the end of the year.

#### **EDUCATION**

### PITMAN TRAINING PETERBOROUGH Web Developer Diploma

(07/2022 - 01/2023)

- Computer and Technology Basics for Developers
- Overview of Software Development
- Version Control
- HTMI
- CSS and Bootstrap
- JavaScript

### Advanced Software and Web Developer Diploma (01/2023 - 03/2023)

- Database and SQL
- Visual Studio
- C# and .NET Framework
- Managing Software Development Projects

## GATESHEAD COLLEGE (COURSE BY SORA GROUP)

#### Functional Skills English and Mathematics

(05/2021 - 07/2021)

- Functional Skills English Level 1
- Functional Skills Mathematics Level 2

### ZESPOL SZKOL NR 5 LUBLIN

Polish Matura (equivalent to A Level)

(09/2012 - 04/2016)

• Hotel industry specialization